Guide to the The Exit Art Archive 1982 - 2011 MSS 343
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibition Files
  - The Reconstruction [2003.01]: Correspondence - Press (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - The Reconstruction [2003.01]: Press Clippings (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Art, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Artists, 2002 - 2003 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Artists, Pablo Helguera (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Census/Population, 2001 - 2002 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Culture, 1999 - 2003 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Accepted Proposals (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Education, 2001 - 2003 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Related Exhibitions (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Food (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Literature, 2001 - 2003 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Latino/a Organizations, 2001 - 2002 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Latino/a Personages (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Music, 2001 - 2003 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Neighborhoods, 2001 - 2003 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Miscellaneous, 2001 - 2003 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Politics, 2002 - 2003 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Theater, 2002 - 2003 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Research - Timeline (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Funding - Research, 2002 - 2003 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Funding - Grant Proposals/Narratives, undated (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Funding - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Funding - Hoy, 2002 - 2003 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Funding - AOL Latino, 2003 - 2004 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Funding - Correspondence, 2002 - 2003 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Call For Proposals, 2002, 2003 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Invitations (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Press Releases (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Publicity - Anne Edgar Associates, 2003 - 2004 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Press Kits (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Exhibition Checklist, undated (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Price List, undated (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Correspondence - General (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Curatorial Texts (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist Projects and Biographies, undated (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist Lists, April 2, 2002 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist Stipends, September 25, 2003 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Contact Lists (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Pamphlet (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Manuel Acevedo (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Andrea Arroyo (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Eduardo Cintron (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Valeria Cordero and Pilita Garcia Esquivel (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Iliana Emelia, 2003 - 2004 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Eduardo Gil (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Nicolas Guagnini (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Linda Irizarry (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Claudia Joskowicz (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Tamara Kostianovsky (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Cristobal Lehyt (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Hermann Mejía and Lucia Pizzani, 2002 - 2004 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Jose Mertz (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Ricardo Miranda Zuniga (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Maritza Molina (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Marcus Raul Morales (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Felipe Mujica (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Ivan Navarro, 2003 - 2004 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Wanda Raimundi-Ortiz and Edwin Gonzalez, 2003 - 2004 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Freddy Rodriguez (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Milton Rosa-Ortiz (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Karin Schneider (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Courtney Smith (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Xavier Tavera (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Christian Torres Roje (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Johanna Unzuete (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Alex Villar (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Artist File - Johnny The Whip, undated (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Rejected Proposals, A-L (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Rejected Proposals, M-Z, 2002 - 2003 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Loan Information, 2003 - 2004 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Shipping Information, 2003 - 2004 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Exhibition Preparation/Installation Information
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Wall Text/Signs/Labels (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Curated Book Display/Reading Room (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Daily On/Off Instructions, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Public Programs - Overview (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Public Programs - Panel Discussions (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Public Programs - Video Program, 2002 - 2004 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Public Programs - Music Program, 2003 - 2004 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Public Programs - Readings, 2003 - 2004 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Exhibition Tours, 2003 - 2004 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Catalogue, Sales, 2002, 2003 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Budget/Accounting, 2003 - 2004 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Press Research (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Correspondence - Press, 2003 - 2004 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Summary of Media Coverage by Anne Edgar Associates, November 22, 2003 - February 15, 2004 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Exhibition Travel, 2003 - 2004 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - The L Factor [2003.02]: Press Clippings, 2003 - 2004 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Research, Artists A-J, 2003 - 2004 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Research, Artists K-Z, 2003 - 2004 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Research - Exhibitions, 2003 - 2004 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Research - Culture, 2003 - 2004 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Funding - NYSCA, 2000, 2003 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Funding - Israeli Consulate, March 2004 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Call For Proposals, 2003 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Invitations (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Press Release (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Exhibition Checklist, July 2003 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Yochai Avrahami (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Francisca Benitez (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Barbara Broughel (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Laurie Halsey Brown (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Gabo Camnitizer (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Norman Cowie (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Uri Dotan (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Christoph Draeger (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Joy Garnett (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Gideon Gechtman (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Carina Gossele (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Mark Gould (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Cheo Goya (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Michal Heiman
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Michael Hermann (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Robert Hickman (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Saoirse Higgins, 2003 - 2004 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Gary Keown (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Bill Jones, undated, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Fawad Khan, 2004 - 2005 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Kosyo (Kossio Minchev) (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Naomie Kremer (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Peter Kuper (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Michael Laird (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Gillian Laub (Box 109, Folder 25)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Flash Light (Box 109, Folder 26)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Reuben Lorch-Miller (Box 109, Folder 27)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Pedro Lujan (Box 109, Folder 28)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Elahe Massumi (Box 109, Folder 29)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Dennis K. McGinnis (Box 109, Folder 30)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Arnaldo Morales (Box 109, Folder 31)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Joel Murphy (Box 109, Folder 32)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Ivan Navarro (Box 109, Folder 33)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Lior Neiger (Box 109, Folder 34)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Ben Neill (Box 109, Folder 35)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Nurit Newman (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Kevin Noble (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Predrag Pajdic (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Rodrigo Piza (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Frank Raczkowski (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Jayce Salloum (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Martín Sastre (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Simon Schiessl (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Tamar Schori (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Michal Sedaka (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Ariela Shavid (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Mike Peter Smith (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Doron Solomons, 2003 - 2004 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Millette Tapiador (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Florin Tudor (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Claudia X. Valdes (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Liselot van der Heijden (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Mona Vatamanu (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Gal Weinstein (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Paul Wirhun (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Pavel Wolberg (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Michael Zansky (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Francois Zelif (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist File - Anabela Zigova (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Loan Information (Box 110, Folder 25)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Artist Projects & Biographies, undated (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Wall Texts/Signs (Box 110, Folder 27)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Wall Labels (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Curatorial Texts/Narratives, January 2004 (Box 110, Folder 29)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Installation Information/Shipping (Box 110, Folder 30)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Accounting/Expenses (Box 110, Folder 31)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Correspondence, 2003 - 2004 (Box 110, Folder 32)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Opening - Staffing, May 1, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Ongoing Video Screenings - Labels/Lists, undated (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Public Programs - General Information, May 2004 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Public Programs - Screening/Discussion with Jayce Salloum, May 8, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Public Programs - Terrorvision Remixed [Press Release], May 22, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Public Programs - Video Screenings, May 2004 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Public Programs - EAI Curated Video Program, June 2004 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Public Programs - Screening/Discussion with Amy Goodman, July 7, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Deinstallation/Shipping Information (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Correspondence - Press (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Terrorvision [2004.01]: Press Clippings (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Exhibition Proposal, 2002 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Research - Artists (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Research - New Media, 2001 - 2004 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Press Release, June 2004 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Invitations, April - June 2004 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Guest Curator - Michelle Thurz, 2001, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Guest Curator - Anne Ellegood, 2003 - 2004 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Guest Curator - Defne Ayas, June 2004 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Funding, 2002, 2003 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Narrative, undated (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Correspondence, 2002 - 2004 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Artist File - Elena Bajo and Warren Neidich (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Artist File - Tobias Bernstrup (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Artist File - Koken Ergun (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Artist File - Michelle Handelman, June 2004 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Artist File - Will Kwan, August 1, 2004 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Artist File - Serkan Ozkaya (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Artist File - Macie J. Wisniewski, undated (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Artist File - Siebren Versteeg (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Artist File - Ricardo Miranda Zuniga, July 2004 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Installation Information (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Wall Label, undated (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Public Programs, June 2004 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Budget/Accounting (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Public Execution [2004.02]: Press Clippings, June - July 2004 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Research - Artists (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Research - Exhibitions (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Research - Politics [1 of 2] (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Research - Politics [2 of 2], 2003, 2004 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Research - Organizations (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Research - Presidential Portraits, undated (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Call For Proposals, June 2004 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Invitations (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Press Release, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Press Kits, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - 31 Down Radio Theater (Ryan Holsopple) (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Jonathan Allen (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Santiago Antonsanti (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Timothy Blum (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Rutherford Chang (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Lisa Charde (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Sarah Christman and Jen Simmons, 2003 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Mark Cooley (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Lowell Darling, 2003, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Yevgeniy Fiks (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Christy Gast (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Guerilla Girls (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Anthony Hamboussi, 2000, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Packard Jennings, 2003, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Jan Jakub Kotík (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Nate Larson (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Les Leveque (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Flash Light (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Whitney Lynn (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Bonita Makuch (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Mitchell Marco (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Yucef Merhi (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Diane Nerwen (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Nico and Katiushka (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Predrag Pajdic (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Francis Michael Palazzolo (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Christian Pietrapiana (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Jane E. Powers and Monica Sheets (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Michael Rich (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Agatha Wara Romero (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Anne Rowland (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Todd Severson (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Chris Shaw (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Liselot van der Heijden (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Arbuzo Virtmanis (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist File - Cynthia von Buhler (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Artist Projects and Biographies, undated (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Correspondence - General (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Loan Information (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Shipping Information (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Exhibition Checklist, undated (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Wall Labels, undated, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Exhibition Preparation/Installation Information (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Public Programs - General (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Public Programs - Election Night Party, November 2, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Public Programs - Meet the Press, October 24, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Public Programs - Akashic Books Reading, October 13, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Correspondence - Class Tours (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Correspondence - Press (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - The Presidency [2004.03]: Press Clippings, October 2004 (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Invitations, November - December 2004 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Press Release, December 4, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Press Kits, December 4, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Artist List, undated (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Exhibition Checklist (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Price List, undated (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Correspondence, November - December 2004 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Wall Labels, undated (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Installation Information, undated, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Press Clippings (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - The Print Show [2004.04]: Exhibition Travel, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Research, 2004 - 2005 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Call For Proposals, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Invitations (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Invitation Mailing (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Press Release, March 5, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Press Kit, March 5, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Correspondence - General (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist Projects and Biographies (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Sol Aramendi, 2005 - 2006 (Box 115, Folder 20)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - David Borawski, 2004 - 2005 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Michael Combs (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Chaim Garcia (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Reuben Henry (Box 115, Folder 24)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Duron Jackson (Box 115, Folder 25)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Marie-Christine Katz (Box 115, Folder 26)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Sarah Klein (Box 115, Folder 27)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Tamara Kostianovsky (Box 115, Folder 28)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - David Opdyke (Box 115, Folder 29)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Dane Patterson (Box 115, Folder 30)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Richard Rinehart (Box 115, Folder 31)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Bradley Rubenstein and Michael Zansky (Box 115, Folder 32)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Bryan Savitz (Box 116, Folder 1)